LORRAINE BAYNOSA, RN, MSN

Birthplace: Los Angeles, California, U.S.

Language: English
Citizenship United States

Current Work Address: 11301 Wilshire Blvd, Bldg 500, Los Angeles, CA 90073

Personal E-mail Address <u>lorraine.baynosa@gmail.com</u>

Personal cell-phone (818) 390-4187

PROFILE: Operating Room Nurse for nearly 19 years and current full-stack web developer

student at UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp with intention to use coding skills to develop applications to reduce healthcare costs, enhance efficiency of healthcare processes, improve the interoperability of the electronic health record, and reduce the

disparity in delivery of quality care.

EXPERIENCE

2000-2000 Intensive Care Unit Nurse, Cardiothoracic Unit, UCLA Medical Center

2000/11-2006/09 Staff Nurse, Operating Room, VA Greater Los Angeles Healthcare System (VAGLA), West LA Medical Center: Circulating and scrubbing for general, urology, plastic, orthopaedic, hand, ophthalmology, plastic, podiatry, gynecology, head and neck,

vascular, thoracic, cardiac, and neuro surgery

2004-2005 Laparoscopic Service Team Leader, Operating Room, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2006/10-2007/10 Risk Management, Nursing Service, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2006/10-2007/10 MRSA Project Coordinator, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2007/10-2010/07 Nurse Manager, Sterile Processing Services, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2007/06-2015/03 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Per Diem, Saint John's Health Center, Santa

Monica, CA: Circulate and scrub for a myriad of cases including thoracic, vascular, neuro,

spine, general, head & neck, urology, plastics

2014/12-2017/03 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Per Diem, UCLA, Santa Monica Medical Center,

Santa Monica, CA: Contributions as noted above for Saint John's Health Center with greater emphasis on general, orthopaedic, spine, vascular, urology, ENT, plastics procedures;

and exposure to pediatrics cases as well

2010/07-2017/03 Reusable Medical Equipment (RME) Coordinator, VA GLA, West LA Medical Center

2017/03-2017/09 Consultant to Reusable Medical Equipment (RME) Program, VAGLA

2017/03-2018/04 Registered Nurse, Surgery/Operating Room, Kaiser Permanente Santa Clara Medical Center:

Primarily circulator for high-efficiency total joint replacement orthopaedic room

2018/04-current Staff Nurse, Operating Room, VA Greater Los Angeles Healthcare System (VAGLA),

EDUCATION

1995-1997	University of California, Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA
1997-1998	Los Angeles Community College, Los Angeles, CA

1998-2000 B.S. University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA in Nursing 2004-2006 M.S. University of California, Los Angeles, CA in Nursing Administration

2019-current UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp, Full-Stack Web Developer

SKILLS:

HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, Materialize), JQuery, Javascript, Firebase Realtime Database, Ajax calls, Google Maps API

LANGUAGES:

HTML, JavaScript

REFERENCES:

Available upon request.